Guide to the Actors' Equity Association Theatrical Programs WAG.257
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
Actors' Equity Association Theatrical Programs
1915-2001
WAG.257
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
61.0 linear feet (61 boxes)
Actors' Equity Association (AEA) is the union of professional legitimate stage actors and stage managers. AEA negotiates contracts and agreements that often affect a productions theatre program. Over the years rules regarding billing, program biographies, and Equity recognition in programs have become part of these contracts and agreements. The Actors' Equity Association Theatrical Programs collection is made up of programs collected by the organization, its employees and friends from 1915 to 2001. The collection includes programs for productions in New York City, at regional theatres around the country as well as touring productions and Equity Library Theatre. The collection demonstrates the enormity and diversity of theatre in America during the 20th Century.
Actors' Equity Association.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Through a vote of its governing Council in late 1981, Actors' Equity Association designated the Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives at New York University the official repository of its historical records. The first shipment of records arrived at the archives in 1982. Since then several additional donations of material have been made, including these theatrical programs that arrived in 2002. The accession number associated with this gift is 2002.006. Additional donations were received from Ann H. Greenberg in 2007, and Stacey Burkhard in 2009.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
Actors' Equity Association (AEA) is the union of professional legitimate stage actors and stage managers. It was founded in New York City in May 1913, but did not gain full recognition as the bargaining agent for actors until the historic strike of 1919.
AEA negotiates contracts and agreements that often affect a productions theatre program. Over the years rules regarding billing, program biographies, and Equity recognition in programs have become part of these contracts and agreements.
The bulk of the programs in this collection came from Paul Ross. An Equity stage manager, Ross was the publisher of the Players' Guide, a compilation of actors' photographs and credits arranged by sex and type. He collected these programs from Equity representatives who attended shows as well as from his own participation. He used them primarily to check credits for inclusion in the guide.
The staff of Actors' Equity also uses programs to determine if all contractual obligations have been fulfilled and if a member is under the correct contract (principal or chorus). Some of the programs in the collection, most often from the 1930s, include notes but it is unclear under what circumstances these notes occurred since Equity would usually put a program with notes in an individual production file.
Demonstrating the enormity and diversity of theatre in America during the 20th Century, the collection gives more than just a list of players in a given production. The programs offer a look into how productions were presented, how advertising changed over the years, and how some productions continue to be produced generation after generation.
Scope and Content Note
The Actors' Equity Association Theatrical Programs collection is made up of programs collected by the organization, its employees and friends from 1915 to 2001.
Series: I. New York City, Regional Theatres and Touring Productions/Companies, consists of programs for productions produced in New York City, theatres around the country, touring productions including out-of-town tryouts, and touring companies. The series is arranged alphabetically. The general files that begin each letter are chronological then followed by an alphabetical list of productions and companies. A production is listed individually primarily if it has had more than one production, is of theatrical significance, or ran for an extended period of time.
Series: II. Equity Library Theatre, New York City, Equity Library Theatre (ELT) produced productions from 1944-1989 as a showcase for Equity talent. Because they were a seasonal company the programs for this series are chronological. Production lists and other ELT activities such as children's theatre, informal presentations and benefits are included in the files.
Arrangement
Series I is arranged alphabetically. Series II is arranged chronologically.
The files are grouped into two series:
I, New York City, Regional Theatres and Touring Productions/Companies
II, Equity Library Theatre, New York City
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Actors’ Equity Association: Records (Wagner #11)
Actors' Equity Association.; Chorus Equity Association.; Equity Library Theatre (New York, N.Y.).; Los Angeles (Calif.); New York (N.Y.); Theater programs.; Theater |x United States |x History.; Theater |x United States |x Production and direction.; Theater |z New York (State) |z New York |x History.
- Series I: New York City, Regional Theatres and Touring Productions/Companies
  - A, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A, 1920s (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - A, 1930s (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - A (file 1 of 2), 1940s (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A (file 2 of 2), 1940s (Box 1, Folder 5A)
  - A (file 1 of 2), 1950s (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - A (file 2 of 2), 1950s (Box 1, Folder 6A)
  - A (file 1 of 2), 1960s (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - A (file 2 of 2), 1960s (Box 1, Folder 7A)
  - A (file 1 of 2), 1970s (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - A (file 2 of 2), 1970s (Box 1, Folder 8A)
  - A (file 1 of 2), 1980s (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - A (file 2 of 2), 1980s (Box 1, Folder 9A)
  - A, 1990s (Box 1A, Folder 1)
  - A, 2000s (Box 1A, Folder 2)
  - A…My Name is Alice, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 3)
  - Abe Lincoln in Illinois, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 4)
  - Abelard and Heloise, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 5)
  - Abie's Irish Rose, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 6)
  - Abingdon Square, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 7)
  - Absurd Person Singular, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 8)
  - Accent on Youth, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 9)
  - Accidental Death of an Anarchist, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 10)
  - Acting Company, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 11)
  - Actors Theatre of Louisville, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 12)
  - Adaptation/Next, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 13)
  - Adding Machine, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 14)
  - Adirondack Theatre Festival, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 15)
  - After the Fall, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 16)
  - Agamemnon, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 17)
  - Agnes of God, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 18)
  - Ah, WIlderness, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 19)
  - Ain't Misbehavin', Undated (Box 1A, Folder 20)
  - Ain't Supposed to Die a Natural Death, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 21)
  - Alabama Shakespeare Festival, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 22)
  - Alchemist, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 23)
  - Alice in Wonderland, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 24)
  - All God's Chillun Got Wings, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 25)
  - All in the Timing, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 26)
  - All My Sons, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 27)
  - All Night Strut!, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 28)
  - All Over, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 29)
  - All the King's Men, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 30)
  - All's Well that Ends Well, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 31)
  - Amadeus, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 32)
  - Amen Corner, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 33)
  - America Hurrah, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 34)
  - American Buffalo, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 35)
  - American Clock, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 36)
  - American Dance Machine, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 37)
  - American Conservatory Theatre (ACT San Francisco), Undated (Box 1A, Folder 38)
  - American Musical Theatre Festival, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 39)
  - American Place Theatre, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 40)
  - American Repertory Theatre, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 41)
  - American Shakespeare Festival (Stratford, Connecticut), Undated (Box 1A, Folder 42)
  - American Stage Festival, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 1)
  - American Tragedy, An, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 2)
  - Amphitryon 38, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 3)
  - And A Nightingale Sang, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 4)
  - And Miss Reardon Drinks a Little, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 5)
  - Androcles and the Lion, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 6)
  - Angel Street, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 7)
  - Angels Fall, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 8)
  - Angels in America, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 9)
  - Animal Crackers, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 10)
  - Ankles Aweigh, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 11)
  - Anna Christie, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 12)
  - Anna Lucasta, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 13)
  - Annie, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 14)
  - Annie 2/Annie Warbucks, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 15)
  - Annie Get Your Gun, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 16)
  - Another Part of the Forest, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 17)
  - Antigone, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 18)
  - Antony and Cleopatra, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 19)
  - Any Wednesday, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 20)
  - Anything Goes, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 21)
  - APA-Phoenix Repertory Company, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 22)
  - Applause, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 23)
  - Apple Tree, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 24)
  - Arabian Nights, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 25)
  - Archbishop's Ceiling, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 26)
  - Aspern Papers, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 27)
  - Arcadia, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 28)
  - Aren't We All?, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 29)
  - Arms and the Man, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 30)
  - Arsenic and Old Lace, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 31)
  - Arthur, the Musical, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 32)
  - Artist Descending a Staircase, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 33)
  - Artists and Models: A Novelty Revue, 1924, Paris Edition, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 34)
  - As Is, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 35)
  - As Thousands Cheer, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 36)
  - As You Like It, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 37)
  - Asolo Theatre, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 38)
  - Aspects of Love, Undated (Box 1B, Folder 39)
  - Assassins, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - At the Drop of a Hat; At the Drop of Another Hat, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Au Pair Man, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Aunt Dan and Lemon, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Auntie Mane, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Autumn Garden, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Awake and Sing, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - B, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - B, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - B, 1920s (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - B, 1930s (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - B, 1940s (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - B, 1950s (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - B (file 1 of 2), 1960s (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - B (file 2 of 2), 1960s (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - B (file 1 of 2), 1970s (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - B (file 2 of 2), 1970s (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - B (file 1 of 4), 1980s (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - B (file 2 of 4), 1980s (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - B (file 3 of 4), 1980s (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - B (file 4 of 4), 1980s (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - B (file 1 of 2), 1990s (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - B (file 2 of 2), 1990s (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - B, 2000s (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Baal, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Babes in Arms, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Babes in Toyland, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Baby, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Baby Want a Kiss, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bacchae, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Bachelor Born, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Bad Habits, Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Bad Seed, Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Bajour, Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Baker Street, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Baker's Wife, Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Balcony, Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Ballad of a Sad Café, Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Ballroom, Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Balm in Gilead, Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Band Wagon, Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Banjo Dancing, Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Banjo Eyes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Barefoot in the Park, Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Barnum, Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Barretts of Wimpole Street, Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Barter Theatre, Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Bascom Barlow, Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Basic Training of Pavlo Hummel, Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Bent, Undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Beach House, Undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Beard, Undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Beau Jest, Undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Beautiful People, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Beauty and the Beast, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Beauty Part, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Beaux Stratagem, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Beckett, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bedroom Farce, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Beehive, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Beekman Place, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Beethoven's Tenth, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Before You Go, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Beggar on Horseback, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Beggar's Opera, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Beirut, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Belch, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Bell, Book and Candle, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Bell for Adano, Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Belle of Amherst, Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Bells are Ringing, Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Ben Franklin in Paris, Undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Benefactors, Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Benefit of a Doubt, Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Bent, Undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Berlin to Broadway, Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Best Foot Forward, Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Best Little Whorehouse in Texas; Best Little Whorehouse Goes Public, Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Best Man, Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Betrayal, Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Beverly Hills, Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Beyond the Fringe, Undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Beyond Therapy, Undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Big, Undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Big Deal, Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Big Fish, Little Fish, Undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Big Knife, Undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Big River, Undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Biggest Thief in Town, Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Bill Ross Celebration, Oct 28, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Billion Dollar Baby, Undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Billy Barnes Revue(s), Undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Billy Bishop Goes to War, Undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Billy Budd, Undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Billy Liar, Undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Biloxi Blues, Undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Bingo, Undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Biography, Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Birthday Party, Undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Bistro Car, Undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Black and Blue, Undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Black Comedy, Undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Black Elk Speaks, Undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Black Nativity, Undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Black Picture Show, Undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Black Quartet, Undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Blackbirds of 1928; 1930; 1933-1934 Edition, Undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Blacks, Undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Bless You All, Undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Blind Alley, Undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Blithe Spirit, Undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Blood Brothers, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 1)
  - Blood Knot, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 2)
  - Blood Moon, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 3)
  - Blood, Sweat and Stanley Poole, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 4)
  - Blood Wedding, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 5)
  - Bloomer Girl, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 6)
  - Blossom Time, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 7)
  - Blow Ye Winds, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 8)
  - Blue Denim, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 9)
  - Blue Window, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 10)
  - Blues for Mister Charlie, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 11)
  - Blues in the Night, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 12)
  - Boesman and Lena, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 13)
  - Bonjour, la Bonjour, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 14)
  - Boom Boom Room, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 15)
  - Boor, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 16)
  - Born Yesterday, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 17)
  - Borstal Boy, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 18)
  - Bosoms and Neglect, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 19)
  - Boston Arts Festival, 1964 (Box 4A, Folder 20)
  - Bourgeois Gentilhomme, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 21)
  - Boy Friend, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 22)
  - Boy Meets Girl, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 23)
  - Boys and Girls Together, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 24)
  - Boys from Syracuse, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 25)
  - Boys in the Band, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 26)
  - Boys Next Door, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 27)
  - Breaking Legs, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 28)
  - Breaking the Code, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 29)
  - Brecht on Brecht, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 30)
  - Brief Lives, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 31)
  - Brigadoon, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 32)
  - Brighton Beach Memoirs, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 33)
  - British American Repertory Company (BARC), Undated (Box 4A, Folder 34)
  - Broadway, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 35)
  - Broadway Bound, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 36)
  - Broadway Musical, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 37)
  - Broken Glass, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 38)
  - Brother to Dragons, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 39)
  - Brothers Karamazov, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 40)
  - Browning Version, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 41)
  - Bubbling Brown Sugar, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 42)
  - Buddy: The Buddy Holly Story, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 43)
  - Bullshot Crummond, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 44)
  - Buried Child, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 45)
  - Burlesque, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 46)
  - Burlesque and Variety Entertainment Theatres, 1913-1922 (Box 4A, Folder 47)
  - Burn This, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 48)
  - Bury the Dead, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 49)
  - Bus Stop, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Buskers, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Butley, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Butter and Egg Man, Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Butterfingers Angel, Mary & Joseph, Herod the Nut, and the Slaughter of 12 Hit Carols in a Pear Tree, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Butterflies are Free, Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - By Jupiter, Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - By the Sea By the Sea By the Beautiful Sea, Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Bye Bye Birdie, Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - C, Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - C (file 1 of 2), 1920s (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - C (file 2 of 2), 1920s (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - C, 1930s (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - C, 1940s (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - C (file 1 of 2), 1950s (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - C (file 2 of 2), 1950s (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - C (file 1 of 3), 1960s (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - C (file 2 of 3), 1960s (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - C (file 3 of 3), 1960s (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - C (file 1 of 2), 1970s (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - C (file 2 of 2), 1970s (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - C (file 1 of 3), 1980s (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - C (file 2 of 3), 1980s (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - C (file 3 of 3), 1980s (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - C (file 1 of 2), 1990s (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - C (file 2 of 2), 1990s (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - C, 2000s (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Cabaret, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cabin in the Sky, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Cactus Flower, Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Caesar and Cleopatra, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Café Crown, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Cages, Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Caine Mutiny Court Marshall, Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - California Suite, Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Caligula, Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Call Me By My Rightful Name, Undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Call Me Madam, Undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Camelot, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 1)
  - Can-Can, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 2)
  - Camille, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 3)
  - Camino Real, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 4)
  - Candida, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 5)
  - Candide, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 6)
  - Canterbury Tales, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 7)
  - Captain Brassbound's Conversion, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 8)
  - Captains Courageous, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 9)
  - Caretaker, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 10)
  - Carmen Jones, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 11)
  - Carnival, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 12)
  - Carousel, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 13)
  - Carrie, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 14)
  - Cast Aways, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 15)
  - Cat and the Canary, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 16)
  - Cat and the Fiddler, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 17)
  - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 18)
  - Catch Me If You Can, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 19)
  - Catch 22, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 20)
  - Cats, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 21)
  - Catsplay, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 22)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 23)
  - Cave Dwellers, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 24)
  - Celebrate Broadway, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 25)
  - Champlain Shakespeare Festival, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 26)
  - Changing Room, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 27)
  - Chapter Two, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 28)
  - Charley's Aunt, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 29)
  - Charlot (Andre) Revues, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 30)
  - Cherry Orchard, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 31)
  - Chess, Undated (Box 6A, Folder 32)
  - Chicago[the musical], Undated (Box 6A, Folder 33)
  - Chicago[the play], Undated (Box 6A, Folder 34)
  - Chicken Every Sunday, Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Childe Byron, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Children, Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Children of a Lesser God, Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Children's Hour, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Child's Christmas in Wales, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Child's Play, Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Chocolate Soldier, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Chorus Line, Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Christmas Carol, Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Christmas on Mars, Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Christopher Blake, Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Chu Chem, Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Cinderella, Undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Cindy, Undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Circle, Undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Circle Repertory Company (multiple productions), Undated (Box 7, Folder 16A)
  - City of Angels, Undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - City Stage Company, Undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Clarence Darrow, Undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Clearing in the Woods, Undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Clerambard, Undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Climate of Eden, Undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Clothes for a Summer Hotel, Undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Cloud 9, Undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Club, Undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Coast of Utopia, Undated (Box 7, Folder 25A)
  - Coastal Disturbances, Undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Cocktail Hour, Undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Cocktail Party, Undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Coco, Undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Cold Storage, Undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Cold Wind and the Warm, Undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Colette, Undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Colorado Shakespeare Festival, Undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Colored Museum, Undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Come as You Are, Undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Come Back Little Sheba, Undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Come Blow Your Horn, Undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Comedians, Undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Comedy of Errors, Undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Committee, Undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Common Pursuit, Undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Company, Undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Coming Attractions, Undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Complaisant Lover, Undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Compleat Works of Wllm Shkspr Abridged, Undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Concept, Undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Conduct Unbecoming, Undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Conflict of Interest, Undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Connecticut Yankee, Undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Connection, Undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Constant Wife, Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Consul, Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Contrast, Undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Conversations with My Father, Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Coquette, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Co-Respondent Unknown, Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Coriolanus, Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Corn is Green, Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Corpse!, Undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Cotton Patch Gospel, Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Counsellor-at-Law, Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)